contentkeeper.com 2008-06-12

# ContentKeeper Technologies: Internet Content Filtering Solutions

At ContentKeeper Technologies we are committed to protecting the personal information of our customers. The ContentKeeper privacy policy explains how ContentKeeper protects the privacy of our customers and summarizes how we collect, use and disclose personal information provided by our customers, in accordance with the Australian Commonwealth Privacy Act 1988 (and 2002 amendments). 

**Disclosure to ContentKeeper Technologies of personal information**

When a customer enters into a contract or supply arrangement with ContentKeeper Technologies, through purchasing our goods, we are obliged to collect certain information about the customer. If you choose not to provide any part(s) of your personal information, this may limit or prevent ContentKeeper Technologies from providing the customer with some or all of the services required.

**ContentKeeper Technologies uses the information collected from our customers to:**

  1. Provide services requested by customers;  

  2. Do everything necessary to administer those services;  

  3. Research, develop, manage, protect and improve ContentKeeper’s products and services;  

  4. Conduct customer satisfaction surveys and telephone calls (i.e. “courtesy calls”);  

  5. To inform the customer of any improvements made to the products and services of ContentKeeper Technologies;  

  6. To maintain our database of client information and to track processes for the above purposes;  

  7. To work with the customer to improve service delivery.

As ContentKeeper Technologies is the vendor of the ContentKeeper products and services, we employ a sales channel that requires distributors and resellers to engage directly with customers. Hence, in order to provide customers with excellent service, it is necessary for ContentKeeper and its respective distributors and resellers to exchange information about customers. Distributors require such information in order to allocate clients to their various resellers. Resellers, in turn, require the information to provide customers with services, support and account management on a more local level.

Therefore, customer information may be passed onto the distributors, channel partners and/or resellers, of ContentKeeper products, located in each country or region.

**Protection of your Information**

ContentKeeper Technologies takes all reasonable steps to protect the personal information of our customers. This includes protecting the information from misuse and loss, and from unauthorized access, modification or disclosure. This protection applies to information stored in both electronic and hard copy format. ContentKeeper Technologies will not release customer information to any unauthorized third party. Under no circumstances will ContentKeeper receive payment for or sell customer information.   

**Customer Consent and Agreement**

When the customer provides ContentKeeper Technologies with personal information, they consent to the use and disclosure of that information in accordance with this Privacy Policy, in particular:

  1. The use and disclosure by ContentKeeper Technologies of the information, in order to provide the products and services requested by the customer, and for any other compatible purpose including the management, protection and development of the ContentKeeper Technologies company;
  2. The use and disclosure of information by ContentKeeper Technologies for direct marketing purposes. If the customer does not wish their information to be used for this purpose, they should contact ContentKeeper Technologies. The customer should note, however, that this direct marketing assists ContentKeeper Technologies in continuing to provide the highest level of customer support and to inform the customer on recent ContentKeeper developments.

We hold the privacy of our customers in the highest regard. Thus, under no circumstances will ContentKeeper Technologies sell the personal information of our customers.
